<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Posts on Jazil T S</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Posts on Jazil T S</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 22:34:46 +0530</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        
        <item>
            <title>New Begining</title>
            <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/begin/</link>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 22:34:46 +0530</pubDate>
            
            <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/begin/</guid>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;Starting my blog marks a new chapter in sharing my journey as a Linux enthusiast, UI designer, and ricer. Over the years, I’ve explored various Linux distributions, customized my desktop environment to perfection, and refined my workflow to be as efficient and aesthetic as possible. This blog will serve as a space to document my experiences, from configuring window managers to crafting sleek UI designs that blend form with function. My goal is to provide insights, tutorials, and personal reflections that might help others in their own Linux journey.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Starting my blog marks a new chapter in sharing my journey as a Linux enthusiast, UI designer, and ricer. Over the years, I’ve explored various Linux distributions, customized my desktop environment to perfection, and refined my workflow to be as efficient and aesthetic as possible. This blog will serve as a space to document my experiences, from configuring window managers to crafting sleek UI designs that blend form with function. My goal is to provide insights, tutorials, and personal reflections that might help others in their own Linux journey.</p>
<p><img src="/images/lighthand.jpg" alt="Alt text"></p>
<p>As a Linux ricer, I’ve always been fascinated by the freedom and flexibility Linux offers. Whether it&rsquo;s fine-tuning my system for minimalism or experimenting with new tools to optimize my setup, every tweak brings a sense of accomplishment. My approach to UI design is deeply influenced by my Linux experience, where efficiency and beauty go hand in hand. Through this blog, I aim to showcase my custom setups, share dotfiles, and discuss the thought process behind my design choices. Expect deep dives into Wayland, window managers, and lightweight yet powerful tools that enhance the Linux experience.</p>
<p>This blog isn’t just about aesthetics and customization—it’s also about the philosophy of open-source computing. Linux is more than an operating system; it’s a mindset of exploration, problem-solving, and community-driven innovation. By writing here, I hope to contribute back to the community that has helped me grow over the years. Whether you’re a seasoned Linux user or just getting started, I invite you to join me in this journey of building, refining, and embracing the power of Linux.</p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
